Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reference files, 1976-1993; MS2040 Series 3
  - Publications, West Branch, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Publications, West Branch, 1989-1990 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Western Humanities Review, Summer, 1952 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Western Humanities Review, 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Western Humanities Review, 1987-1991 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Publications, WHACO New Quarterly, Summer, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Publications, What! July/August, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Whetstone, Spring, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Wild Skirt, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Wild Oat Seed, May-July, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The William and Mary Review, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The William and Mary Review, Spring, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Willow Springs, 1980-1982 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Willow Springs, 1983-1985 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Willow Springs, Spring, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Willow Springs 21, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Willow Springs, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Willow Springs, Spring/Winter, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Willow Springs, Summer, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Publications, The Window, February, 1955 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Wisconsin Review, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Woman Image Now, April, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Woman Power, nd, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Publications, World's Word, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Wormwood Review, 1980-1984 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The Wormwood Review, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Publications, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Publications, The Writer's Bar BQ, Autumn, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Publications, The Writer's Bar BQ, Spring/Fall, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Writer's Digest, August-September, 1984-1985 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Writer's Life Line, September, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Writer's Newsletter, February/March, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Publications, WMAC News, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Writer's Forum, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Yale Review, Autumn, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Yarrow, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Yellow Butterfly, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Your Friendly Facist, nd, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Zahir, 1962-1977 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Zelot, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Zeta, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Publications, ZIP, Autumn, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Z Miscellaneous, July, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Z Miscellaneous, November, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Z Miscellaneous, Summer, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Z Miscellaneous, September, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Z Miscellaneous, Spring, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Z Miscellaneous, Fall, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Zone, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Zone 3, Winter, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Publications, ZOOIDS, October, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Publications, ZYZZYVA, 1985-1987 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - The Bloomsbury Review: Sept./Oct. 1981; Nov./Dec. 1981; Feb./Mar. 1982; Apr./May 1982; Nov. 1982; Dec. 1982; Feb./Mar. 1983; Apr./May 1983; Nov. 1983; Dec. 1983; Apr./May 1984; June/July 1984; Aug. 1984; Sept. 1984; Oct. 1984; Dec. 1984; Jan. 1985; Apr. 1985, May 1985; June 1985; July 1985; Sept. 1985; Oct. 1985; Dec. 1985/Jan. 1986; Feb. 1986; Mar. 1986; Apr./May 1986; June 1986; July/Aug. 1986; Fall 1986; Jan./Feb. 1987; May/June 1987; July/Aug. 1987; Sept./Oct. 1987; Nov./Dec. 1987; May/June 1988; July/Aug. 1988; Nov./Dec. 1988; Jan./Feb. 1989; Jan./Feb. 1992; Apr./May 1992; July/Aug. 1992, 1981-1992 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Throttle: Jan./Feb. 1982; May/June 1982; July/August 1982; Sept./Oct. 1982; Nov./Dec. 1982; Jan. 1983; Feb. 1983; Mar. 1983; Apr. 1983; May 1983; June 1983; July 1983; Sept. 1983; Oct. 1983; Nov. 1983; Dec. 1983; Jan. 1984; Feb. 1984; Mar. 1984; Apr. 1984; May 1984; July 1984; Oct. 1984; Dec. 1984; Jan. 1985; Feb. 1985; Mar. 1985; May 1985; June 1985; July/Aug. 1985; Sept. 1985; Oct. 1985; Dec. 1985; Feb. 1987; May 1987, 1982-1987 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - The Washington Tribune: May 20-June 3, 1978; Sept. 23-Oct. 7, 1978; June 1979; Dec. 1979; Nov. 1980, undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - The Washington Tribune: Jan. 29-Feb. 11, 1982; Feb. 12-25, 1982; Feb. 26-Mar. 11, 1982; Mar. 12-25, 1982, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - The Washington Tribune: Jan. 13, 1983; Jan. 27, 1983; Feb. 17, 1983; Feb. 24, 1983; Mar. 3, 1983; Mar. 24, 1983; Mar. 31, 1983; Apr. 14, 1983; Apr. 21, 1983; Apr. 28, 1983; May 5, 1983; May 12, 1983, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - The Washington Weekly: June 18, 1984; June 25, 1984; July 2, 1984; July 9, 1984; July 16, 1984; July 23, 1984; July 30, 1984; Aug. 6/13, 1984; Aug. 20, 1984; Aug. 27, 1984; Sept. 3, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - The Washington Weekly: December 31 & January 1985; January 18, 1985; January 25, 1985; February 1, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Adams Morgan Celebration Journal, Sept. 28, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Alexandria Tribune, March 8, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The American Poetry Review, Nov/Dec, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Art and Artists, vol. 15, no. 4, July/Aug, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Artscapes, Jan March, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. IV, no. 4, July Aug., 1991 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VIII, no. 1, Aug., 1981 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Eye Wash, vol. 1, no. 3, April, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. 3, no. 7, March, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VII, no. 12, July, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VII, no. 11, June, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VII, no. 9, April, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VII, no. 8, March, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VII, no. 7, Feb., 1988 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VII, no. 6, Jan., 1987 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Arts focus, vol. VII, no. 5, Dec., 1987 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Publications, The Arts Journal, Feb., 1984 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Publications, The Arts Journal, vol. 4, no. 12, September, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Publications, Artspiral, Winter, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Publications, Artspiral, vol. 6, Summer, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Publications, Arts Washington, vol. 10, no. 7, Sept., 1987 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Publications, Arts Washington, vol. 10, no. 7, Sept., 1987 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Publications, Arts Washington, vol. 11, no.6, July/Aug., 1988 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Publications, AWP Chronicle, vol. 25, no. 2, Oct/Nov., 1992 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Publications, AWP Chronicle, vol.23, no. 2, Oct/Nov., 1990 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Publications, AWP Newsletter, Feb/March, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Publications, AWP Newsletter, Sept/Oct, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Publications, AWP Newsletter, Nov/Dec, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Publications, Back Country, no.8, Fall, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 29)
  - Publications, Bethesda Co op News, March, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Publications,Borders Review of Books, Jan/Feb, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - Publications, Borders Review of Books, vol. VI, no. IV, May, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 32)
  - Publications, Black Arts Review, vol. 1, no. 2, Sept., 1978 (Box 116, Folder 33)
  - Publications, Black Arts Review, vol. II, no. 3, May June, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 34)
  - Publications, Black Arts Review, vol. II, no. 2, July Aug., undated (Box 116, Folder 35)
  - Publications, Black Arts Review, vol. II, no. 4, Nov/Dec., undated (Box 116, Folder 36)
  - Publications, The Buddhist Thirdclass; Junkmail Oracle, May, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 37)
  - Publications, Cedar Rock, vol. 6, no. 3, Summer, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 38)
  - Publications, Cedar Rock, Winter, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 39)
  - Publications, Cedar Rock, Fall, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 40)
  - Publications, Center City, vol. 1, no. 2, June, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 41)
  - Publications, Chiron Review, vol. VIII, no. 4, Winter, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 42)
  - Publications, Chiron Review, vol. VIII, no. 2, Summer, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 43)
  - Publications, Chiron Review, vol. IX, no. 3, Autumn, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 44)
  - Publications, Crack D.C, June, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 45)
  - Publications, Crack D.C, August, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 46)
  - Publications, Crack D.C, September, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 47)
  - Publications, DC Home News, vol. 1, no. 1, Nov. 15, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Diarist's Journal, first issue, Jan., 1988 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Eye Wash, vol. 4, no. 4, April, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Fashion Flash, November, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Fashion Flash, vol. 1, no. 8, undated (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Fashion Flash, March, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Fashion Flash, April, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Fashion Flash, Summer, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Fashion Flash, March, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Fashion Flash, October, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Fiction Monthly, vol. 2, no. 10, Summer, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Fiction Monthly, vol. 2, no. 9, May, undated (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Fiction Monthly, vol. 2, no. 8, April, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Fiction Monthly, vol. 2, no. 7, March, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Fiction Monthly, vol. 2, no. 6, Feb, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Publications, GET, vol.1, no.3, undated (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Publications, Ice River, Vol. 4.2, Summer, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Publications, The In Towner, vol.7, no.8, March, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Publications, Jamm, no.4, Spring, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Publications, KC Pitch, no. 85, Jan., 1988 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Publications, Key DC, vol.1, no.2, May 3, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Publications, Key DC, vol.1, no.3, May 17, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Publications, The Kindred Spirit, no.4, Sept. 20, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Publications, The Kindred Spirit; A Poetry Journal, no. 8, Feb, 19, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Publications, The Kindred Spirit; A Poetry Journal, no. 11, Spring, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Publications, The Kindred Spirit; A Poetry Journal, no. 16, undated (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Publications, The Kindred Spirit, vol VII, no.2, Summer, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Publications, The Kindred Spirit, vol. VII, no.3, Winter, 1988-1989 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Publications, King Street Chronicle, Jan., 1984 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Publications,King Street Chronicle, March, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Publications, Poetry, San Francisco, no. 12, Autumn, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Letras Da Provincia, vol. IV, no. 42, undated (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Litmus Inc., undated (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Milkweed Chronicle, vol. 7, no. 1, Winter, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Milkweed Chronicle, vol. 6, no. 3, Fall, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The New Paper, vol.2, no. 50, Oct. 31, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Newsworks, no. 3, Feb. 26 March 3, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Newsworks, no. 9, April 11 17, undated (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Newsworks, no. 31, Sept. 23 29, undated (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Publications, New Virginia Review; Newsletter, March, 1982 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Publications, No Comment, vol. 1, no. 5, Sept., 1985 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Publications, No Comment, vol. 1, no. 6, October, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Poet News, September, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Poetry Flash, no. 187, Oct., 1988 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Poetry Flash, no. 159, June, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Poetry Flash, no. 122, May, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Publications, Poetry Flash, no. 131, Feb, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Publications, Poetry Flash, no. 168, March, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Publications, Poetry Flash, no. 169, April, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Publications, Rio Magazine, March, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Publications, Rock Creek Monitor, May 11, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Publications, Rock Creek Monitor, May 3, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Publications, Rock Creek Monitor, June 28, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Publications, Rock Creek Monitor, August 14, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Publications, Rock Creek Monitor, Sept. 19 Oct. 17, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Publications, The Southwestern Review, vol. 6, no. 8, undated (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Publications, THIS magazine, vol. 1, no. 3, Dec., 1982 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Publications, THIS magazine, vol. 1, no. 2, Oct., 1962 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - Publications, U & dc., vol. 14, no. 3, November, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 29)
  - Publications, U & dc., vol. 20, no. 1, Spring, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - Publications, U & dc., vol. 19, no. 2, Summer, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - Publications, U & dc., vol. 17, no. 4, Fall, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Publications, U & dc., vol. 19, no. 1, Spring, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - Publications, U & dc., vol. 18, no. 4, Winter, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - Publications, U & dc., vol. 18, no. 2, Summer, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - Publications, The Washington Boast, no. 1, April 1, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Gallery/Museum News, vol. I, no. 2, Oct., 1983 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Gallery/Museum News, vol. I, no. 1, Sept., 1983 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Gallery/Museum News, vol. II, no. 1, Jan., 1984 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Gallery/Museum News, vol. II, no. 2, March, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Gallery/Museum News, vol. II, no. 3, May, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Gallery/Museum News, vol. II, no. 4, Summer, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Washington City Paper, vol. 1, no. 1, Nov., 1989 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Western Publisher, vol. 1, no. 1, Oct., 1980 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Whack, Oct., 1991 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Whack, Dec., 1991 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Whack, Jan., 1992 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Whack, March, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Whack, May, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Whack, first anniversary issue, undated (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Worth Less Words, undated (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Art Lines, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Artist Trust, 1991-1993 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Aura, 1978-1979 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - New Boston Review, 1978-1984 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Boxcar, Winter-Spring, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - The Charles Street Paper, February, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - The Chesapeake Arts Cultural Calendar, January February, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Dark Horse, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Duckberg Times, 1985-1987 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Flue, Volume 1, Number 4, undated (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Fragments, Issue no. 15/16, undated (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Free Spirit, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Funny Times, September, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - The Washington Globe, October 9, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Headliners, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Hungry Mind Review, 1986-1990 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Lake Effect, Summer, 1989 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Literary Network Newsletter, undated (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - London Review of Books, 1987-1988 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Lynn Voices, June, 1980 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - This Month in Maine Literature, July, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - The New Art Examiner, 1980-1984 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - News Art, 1978-1981 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - The New Commercialist, 1981 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - The Paper Hat, nd, undated (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Piedmont Virginian, July 7, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Reflex, September/October, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco Review of Books, 1981-1987 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - The Washington Times, 1976 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - The Times Literary Supplement, January 21, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Truly Fine Press, Volume 6, Number 1, undated (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - University Publishing, 1979-1985 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Washington Scene, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Washington After Dark, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Washington Art Reporter, 1987-1988 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - What, 1986-1987 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - The Women's Review of Books, March, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - The American Book Review, 1978-1981 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Northern Lit Quarterly, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - The Pikestaff Forum, 1978-1986 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - The Three Penny Review, 1982-1990 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - City Paper Baltimore, 1978-1980 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - City Paper Baltimore, 1980-1981 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - City Paper Baltimore, 1982 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - City Paper Baltimore, 1983 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - City Paper Baltimore, 1983 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1982-1983 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1984 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1984 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1986-1987 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1987 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - City Paper DC, 1987-1988 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- Production files, Circa 1970-1992; MS2040 Series 4
  This series primarily contains material generated in the production of Gargoyle such as galleys, blue lines, page mechanicals, negatives and original manuscripts submitted by authors for publication in the magazine.
  Included are original manuscripts, negatives and page mechanicals for other Paycock Press publications, such as The Love Letter Hack, Blank Like Me, I'm in Love With the Morton Salt Girl, Jukebox and The Natural History, have also been saved.
  The series measures 22 linear feet.
  - Production Files, MS, Jacqueline Bowles, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, MS, Alexander Blackburn, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, MS, Katie Brady, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, MS, John Brand, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, MS, Jerry Bumpus, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, MS, J.D. Buttinger, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, MS, Grace Calvieleri, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, MS, Bonnie Chasteen, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, MS, DeWitt Clinton, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, MS, Mitch Cohen, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, MS, Kaz Deru, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, MS, Reywas Divad, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, MS, Lindsay E. Edmunds, undated (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, MS, Ken Edwards, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, MS, Nik Elevitch, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, MS, Johanna Ellsworth, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Production Files, MS, William Gerber, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - Production Files, MS, Amy Gerstler, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - Production Files, MS, Jane Gibson, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - Production Files, MS, Allan Gilbertson, 1977-1978 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Production Files, MS, Katherine Gillman, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 21)
  - Production Files, MS, Jesse Glass, Jr., 1976 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Production Files, MS, Richard Grayson, 1978 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Production Files, MS, Mark Greenside, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Production Files, MS, George Haessler, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 25)
  - Production Files, MS, Tom Hazuka, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 26)
  - Production Files, MS, David Hickman, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 27)
  - Production Files, MS, John Hooe, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 28)
  - Production Files, MS, Francine Horowitz, nd, undated (Box 142, Folder 29)
  - Production Files, MS, Herbert Huncke, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, MS, Herbert Huncke, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, MS, Jape Iros, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, MS, Philip K. Jason, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, MS, Gerald Kariniemi, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, MS, Sonya Keene, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, MS, Thomas Kennedy, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, MS, Jascha Kessler, undated (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, MS, R. V. Jason, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, MS, E.J. Kovats, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, MS, John Lewis, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, MS, James Maher, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, MS, Kevin Maney, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, MS, Susan Mernit, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, MS, Brown Miller, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, MS, Michael J. Milligan, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Production Files, MS, Peter Mortimer, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Production Files, MS, V.M. Nelson, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Production Files, MS, David O'Dell, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Production Files, MS, Barry Edgar Pilcher, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Production Files, MS, Carlo Purcelli, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Production Files, MS, Joseph Raffa, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Production Files, MS, Ian Robinson, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Production Files, MS, Joseph Ross, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 24)
  - Production Files, MS, Betty Rutherford, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 25)
  - Production Files, MS, Patrick Saari, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 26)
  - Production Files, MS, Robert Sandmeyer, nd, undated (Box 143, Folder 27)
  - Production Files, MS, Jack Saunders, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 28)
  - Production Files, MS, Harold Schneider, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - Production Files, MS, Lynn Sheridan, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - Production Files, MS, A.M. Skye, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 31)
  - Production Files, MS, Dave Slater, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 32)
  - Production Files, MS, Robert J. Solomon, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 33)
  - Production Files, MS, Kenneth R. Timmerman, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 34)
  - Production Files, MS, Kenneth R. Timmerman, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 35)
  - Production Files, MS, Kenneth R. Timmerman, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 36)
  - Production Files, MS, Unknown, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 37)
  - Production Files, MS, Unknown, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 38)